



// function moveChar() {

//   }

// $('#id').click(function getUsername(){
//   $('.lpInput').val();
// })

// function getUsername() {
//     document.getElementById("lpInput").value;
//     console.log(un)
// $(document).ready(function(un){
//     $('').append(un);
//     console.log($("#username"))
// })
// }

var cat1_1 = {
  question: "Is this the first question?",
  ans1: "Maybe",
  ans2: "Yes",
  ans3: "No",
  id: "cat1.100",
  pointVal: 100,
  answer: [2]
}


$('#r1c1').click(function () {
  $('.questionDiv').css('display', 'block');
  $('.amount').html(cat1_1.pointVal);
  $('#ques').html(cat1_1.question);
  $('#firstBttn').html(cat1_1.ans1);
  $('#secondBttn').html(cat1_1.ans2);
  $('#thirdBttn').html(cat1_1.ans3);
  $('#charDiv').animate({marginRight:"200px"}, 800);
})

var cat2_1 = {
  question: "Is this the Second question?",
  ans1: "Maybe",
  ans2: "Yes",
  ans3: "No",
  id: "cat2.100",
  pointVal: 100,
  answer: [2]
}

$('#r1c2').click(function () {
  $('.questionDiv').css('display', 'block');
  $('.amount').html(cat2_2.pointVal);
  $('#ques').html(cat2_1.question);
  $('#firstBttn').html(cat2_1.ans1);
  $('#secondBttn').html(cat2_1.ans2);
  $('#thirdBttn').html(cat2_1.ans3);
  $('#charDiv').animate({marginRight:"200px"}, 800);
})

var cat3_1 = {
  question: "Is this the third question?",
  ans1: "Maybe",
  ans2: "Yes",
  ans3: "No",
  id: "cat3.100",
  pointVal: 100,
  answer: [2]
}

$('#r1c3').click(function () {
  $('.questionDiv').css('display', 'block');
  $('.amount').html(cat3_2.pointVal);
  $('#ques').html(cat3_1.question);
  $('#firstBttn').html(cat3_1.ans1);
  $('#secondBttn').html(cat3_1.ans2);
  $('#thirdBttn').html(cat3_1.ans3);
  $('#charDiv').animate({marginRight:"200px"}, 800);
})

var cat4_1 = {
  question: "Is this the fourth question?",
  ans1: "Maybe",
  ans2: "Yes",
  ans3: "No",
  id: "cat4.100",
  pointVal: 100,
  answer: [2]
}

$('#r1c4').click(function () {
  $('.questionDiv').css('display', 'block');
  $('.amount').html(cat4_1.pointVal);
  $('#ques').html(cat4_1.question);
  $('#firstBttn').html(cat4_1.ans1);
  $('#secondBttn').html(cat4_1.ans2);
  $('#thirdBttn').html(cat4_1.ans3);
  $('#charDiv').animate({marginRight:"200px"}, 800);
})

var cat1_2 = {
  question: "What is the name of Angelica's cat?",
  ans1: "Fluffy",
  ans2: "Snowflake",
  ans3: "Princess",
  id: "cat1.200",
  pointVal: 200,
  answer: "#firstBttn"
}

$('#r2c1').click(function () {
  $('.questionDiv').css('display', 'block');
  $('.amount').html(cat1_2.pointVal);
  $('#ques').html(cat1_2.question);
  $('#firstBttn').html(cat1_2.ans1);
  $('#secondBttn').html(cat1_2.ans2);
  $('#thirdBttn').html(cat1_2.ans3);
  $('#charDiv').animate({marginRight:"200px"}, 800);
})

var cat2_2 = {
  question: "Is this the fourth question?",
  ans1: "Maybe",
  ans2: "Yes",
  ans3: "No",
  id: "cat2.200",
  pointVal: 200,
  answer: [2]
}

$('#r2c2').click(function () {
  $('.questionDiv').css('display', 'block');
  $('.amount').html(cat2_2.pointVal);
  $('#ques').html(cat2_2.question);
  $('#firstBttn').html(cat2_2.ans1);
  $('#secondBttn').html(cat2_2.ans2);
  $('#thirdBttn').html(cat2_2.ans3);
  $('#charDiv').animate({marginRight:"200px"}, 800);
})

var cat3_2 = {
  question: "Is this the fourth question?",
  ans1: "Maybe",
  ans2: "Yes",
  ans3: "No",
  id: "cat3.200",
  pointVal: 200,
  answer: [2]
}

$('#r2c3').click(function () {
  $('.questionDiv').css('display', 'block');
  $('.amount').html(cat3_2.pointVal);
  $('#ques').html(cat3_2.question);
  $('#firstBttn').html(cat3_2.ans1);
  $('#secondBttn').html(cat3_2.ans2);
  $('#thirdBttn').html(cat3_2.ans3);
  $('#charDiv').animate({marginRight:"200px"}, 800);
})

var cat4_2 = {
  question: "Is this the fourth question?",
  ans1: "Maybe",
  ans2: "Yes",
  ans3: "No",
  id: "cat4.200",
  pointVal: 200,
  answer: [2]
}

$('#r2c4').click(function () {
  $('.questionDiv').css('display', 'block');
  $('.amount').html(cat4_2.pointVal);
  $('#ques').html(cat4_2.question);
  $('#firstBttn').html(cat4_2.ans1);
  $('#secondBttn').html(cat4_2.ans2);
  $('#thirdBttn').html(cat4_2.ans3);
  $('#charDiv').animate({marginRight:"200px"}, 800);
})

var cat1_3 = {
  question: "What does Angelica get from the Tooth Fairy for her tooth?",
  ans1: "A penny",
  ans2: "A note",
  ans3: "A dime",
  id: "cat1.400",
  pointVal: 400,
  answer: "#thirdBttn"
}


$('#r3c1').click(function () {
  $('.questionDiv').css('display', 'block');
  $('.amount').html(cat1_3.pointVal);
  $('#ques').html(cat1_3.question);
  $('#firstBttn').html(cat1_3.ans1);
  $('#secondBttn').html(cat1_3.ans2);
  $('#thirdBttn').html(cat1_3.ans3);
  $('#charDiv').animate({marginRight:"200px"}, 800);
})

var cat2_3 = {
  question: "Is this the fourth question?",
  ans1: "Maybe",
  ans2: "Yes",
  ans3: "No",
  id: "cat2.400",
  pointVal: 400,
  answer: [2]
}

$('#r3c2').click(function () {
  $('.questionDiv').css('display', 'block');
  $('.amount').html(cat2_3.pointVal);
  $('#ques').html(cat2_3.question);
  $('#firstBttn').html(cat2_3.ans1);
  $('#secondBttn').html(cat2_3.ans2);
  $('#thirdBttn').html(cat2_3.ans3);
  $('#charDiv').animate({marginRight:"200px"}, 800);
})

var cat3_3 = {
  question: "Is this the fourth question?",
  ans1: "Maybe",
  ans2: "Yes",
  ans3: "No",
  id: "cat3.400",
  pointVal: 400,
  answer: [2]
}

$('#r3c3').click(function () {
  $('.questionDiv').css('display', 'block');
  $('.amount').html(cat3_3.pointVal);
  $('#ques').html(cat3_3.question);
  $('#firstBttn').html(cat3_3.ans1);
  $('#secondBttn').html(cat3_3.ans2);
  $('#thirdBttn').html(cat3_3.ans3);
  $('#charDiv').animate({marginRight:"200px"}, 800);
})

var cat4_3 = {
  question: "Is this the fourth question?",
  ans1: "Maybe",
  ans2: "Yes",
  ans3: "No",
  id: "cat4.400",
  pointVal: 400,
  answer: [2]
}

$('#r3c4').click(function () {
  $('.questionDiv').css('display', 'block');
  $('.amount').html(cat4_3.pointVal);
  $('#ques').html(cat4_3.question);
  $('#firstBttn').html(cat4_3.ans1);
  $('#secondBttn').html(cat4_3.ans2);
  $('#thirdBttn').html(cat4_3.ans3);
  $('#charDiv').animate({marginRight:"200px"}, 800);
})

var cat1_4 = {
  question: "Angelica diagnoses Chuckie with what illness?",
  ans1: "Clownophobia",
  ans2: "Rhinoceritis",
  ans3: "Reptar fever",
  id: "cat1.800",
  pointVal: 800,
  answer: "#secondBttn"
}


$('#r4c1').click(function () {
  $('.questionDiv').css('display', 'block');
  $('.amount').html(cat1_4.pointVal);
  $('#ques').html(cat1_4.question);
  $('#firstBttn').html(cat1_4.ans1);
  $('#secondBttn').html(cat1_4.ans2);
  $('#thirdBttn').html(cat1_4.ans3);
  $('#charDiv').animate({marginRight:"200px"}, 800);
})

var cat2_4 = {
  question: "Is this the fourth question?",
  ans1: "Maybe",
  ans2: "Yes",
  ans3: "No",
  id: "cat2.800",
  pointVal: 800,
  answer: [2]
}

$('#r4c2').click(function () {
  $('.questionDiv').css('display', 'block');
  $('.amount').html(cat2_4.pointVal);
  $('#ques').html(cat2_4.question);
  $('#firstBttn').html(cat2_4.ans1);
  $('#secondBttn').html(cat2_4.ans2);
  $('#thirdBttn').html(cat2_4.ans3);
  $('#charDiv').animate({marginRight:"200px"}, 800);
})

var cat3_4 = {
  question: "Is this the fourth question?",
  ans1: "Maybe",
  ans2: "Yes",
  ans3: "No",
  id: "cat3.800",
  pointVal: 800,
  answer: [2]
}

$('#r4c3').click(function () {
  $('.questionDiv').css('display', 'block');
  $('.amount').html(cat3_4.pointVal);
  $('#ques').html(cat3_4.question);
  $('#firstBttn').html(cat3_4.ans1);
  $('#secondBttn').html(cat3_4.ans2);
  $('#thirdBttn').html(cat3_4.ans3);
  $('#charDiv').animate({marginRight:"200px"}, 800);
})

var cat4_4 = {
  question: "Is this the fourth question?",
  ans1: "Maybe",
  ans2: "Yes",
  ans3: "No",
  id: "cat4.800",
  pointVal: 800,
  answer: [2]
}

$('#r4c4').click(function () {
  $('.questionDiv').css('display', 'block');
  $('.amount').html(cat4_4.pointVal);
  $('#ques').html(cat4_4.question);
  $('#firstBttn').html(cat4_4.ans1);
  $('#secondBttn').html(cat4_4.ans2);
  $('#thirdBttn').html(cat4_4.ans3);
  $('#charDiv').animate({marginRight:"200px"}, 800);
})